jumpseller.com 2019-07-31

# Our Privacy Policy

Support

[WIDETAIL, Lda.](http://widetail.com/) (hereinafter referred to as, **WIDETAIL** ) with tax number PT 509 168 930 and headquartered at at Rua Actor Ferreira da Silva, 100, 4200 - 298 Porto, Portugal is a Portuguese company dedicated, among other activities, to the development and management of the web platform Jumpseller (hereinafter referred to as **PLATFORM** ).

WIDETAIL IS COMMITTED TO PROTECTING YOUR PRIVACY, AND HAS THEREFORE DEVELOPED THIS PRIVACY POLICY TO EXPLAIN HOW YOUR PERSONAL DATA IS COLLECTED, PROCESSED AND DISCLOSED BY ITS PLATFORM. WE ADVISE EVERYONE TO READ IT CAREFULLY, IN ORDER TO BECOME FAMILIAR WITH OUR PRIVACY PRACTICES.

* * *

## Scope and Coverage

This Privacy Policy applies only to the collection and processing of personal data carried out by WIDETAIL for the provision of services through the PLATFORM, allowing those services to be provided expeditiously and without inconvenience to the USERS.

Users can navigate through parts of the PLATFORM without having to register, however, it is necessary to register to be able to make use of certain features, in particular those that enable the operations of the online stores.

* * *

## Personal Data

Personal data means any information in any nature and/or medium relating to an identified or identifiable person, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to one or more specific elements, whether of their identity or their private life.

* * *

## Purpose

The collected personal data is an essential tool for USERS' satisfaction and that personal data is processed in accordance with the applicable law and best practices.  
WIDETAIL uses this data in an appropriate and expected way for the provision of its PLATFORM services, namely, to:

### For Merchants

  1. enable the services that facilitate the operations of their online store;
  2. setup the USERS accounts and profiles;
  3. improve the contents of the service;
  4. report news about the PLATFORM;
  5. adapt the services to the needs of its USERS;
  6. allow the development of new features;
  7. improve and personalize our services;
  8. provide support.

### For Customers

  1. provide our Merchants with the services, including supporting and processing orders, risk and fraud screening, authentication, and payments;
  2. estimate shipping and taxes;
  3. pre-fill checkout information;
  4. improve our services.

### For Partners

  1. confirm identity and contact the partner;
  2. make payments;
  3. screen for risk, fraud, or other similar issues.

* * *

## Data Collected

### From Merchants

WIDETAIL collects and processes personal data necessary for the provision of services, to its operations and PLATFORM management, namely, username, name, email address, billing information, postal address, date of registration and of the last login.

When using the service, the PLATFORM can automatically register in its servers general data, such as the User Agent of the Browser, IP address and requested pages.

### From Customers

WIDETAIL collects the Marchants' Customers:

  * name;
  * email;
  * shipping and billing address;
  * tax id;
  * payment details;
  * company name;
  * phone number;
  * information about orders you initiate, and
  * general data, such as the User Agent of the Browser, IP address & requested pages.

### From partners

WIDETAIL collects the partner's:

  * name;
  * company name;
  * website;
  * twitter - or other social media handles;
  * phone number(s);
  * address;
  * business type;
  * email address;
  * PayPal Account, and
  * tax number.

* * *

## How Data is Collected

The data will be collected through forms and through the PLATFORM's usage, after the USER acknowledges the collection and consents to its processing, which is made according to the law. The collected data is stored on secure servers. The personal data collected will not be used, in any situation, for any purpose other than that for which consent was previously obtained.

* * *

## Cookies

To make this site work properly, we place small data files called cookies on your device. Most big websites do this too.

A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you don't have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another.

WIDETAIL uses cookies for:

  1. Provide the services you are using. Those cookies are essential;  

  2. Other cookies allow the website to remember choices you make;  

  3. Some are used to understand how the PLATFORM users interact and use our products and services; and,  

  4. Other might be used to advertising purposes that WIDETAIL believes that might be relevant to you.

These cookies are not used to target you with online marketing.

WIDETAIL does not use cookies for any purpose other than the ones listed in this policy. By using our website, you agree that cookies may be placed on your computer or internet-enabled device.

You can control and/or delete cookies as you wish – for details, see [allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit the site and some services and functionalities may not work.

These are the cookies WIDETAIL uses in the PLATFORM:

COOKIE | FUNCTION  
---|---  
_unam  
_utmx  
_utmxx  
_ga  
_gat  |  [Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/types)  
_zlcmid  | Zopim Live Chat  
jumpseller_referrer jumpseller_referrerid  | Jumpseller Referrer Data  
mp_*  | Mixpanel  
rack.session  | Jumpseller Session Persistence  
  
* * *

## Users and Security

WIDETAIL takes the security of personal information very seriously, and does its best to safeguard it. Keeping in mind the state of the art and the technical knowledge available, WIDETAIL uses technical and organizational measures to protect personal data against destruction, accidental or unlawful loss, accidental alteration, disclosure or unauthorized access, within a level of security appropriate to the nature of the data being protected. However, WIDETAIL cannot guarantee the total security of the information of its USERS' accounts against all possible situations of unauthorized access, hardware or software failures and other factors that may compromise the security of the information.  
USERS should make a careful use of the PLATFORM in order to prevent unauthorized access to their accounts and personal information, namely, by carefully selecting and protecting their passwords and limiting access to the devices through which they access the PLATFORM.  
WIDETAIL encrypts data sent to and from Merchants and Customers using the HTTPS protocol. Jumpseller also encrypts any sensitive stored information, and salts and hashes Merchant and Customer passwords using bcrypt. 

* * *

## Storage Period

Personal data will be stored and kept only for the lifespan of each USER's account, either by cancellation, suspension or lack of use of the PLATFORM, as referred in the Terms and Conditions. This period is deemed to be sufficient for the purposes for which the personal data was collected. After this period, any personal data collected is eliminated after 30 days.  
Encrypted backups will be kept up to 5 years after account termination. Logs are kept for a maximum period of 90 days, unless required to be kept for longer periods by law.

* * *

## Rectification

You may update your personal data at any time through the USER's area in the PLATFORM.  
If you are unable to update his personal data that way, you should contact WIDETAIL via the proper contact form requesting this rectification, erasure, update and/or modification, of which they will be notified by email as soon as it occurs.

* * *

## Right of Access

Data protection laws grant you the right to access your personal data at any time, as well as the right to oppose the use of the provided personal data. To this purpose, you should submit a written request through the proper contact form.

* * *

## Elimination

You may eliminate their personal data at any time through the termination of your account. However some of the personal data may be stored for a longer period of time, as detailed above.

* * *

## Metrics

WIDETAIL uses statistical information gathering services, which collect anonymous information about the PLATFORM's usage, for example, time of visits, pages viewed and type of operating system used. These services are:

  1. Google Analytics is a traffic analysis service provided by Google, Inc. ("GOOGLE") used in the PLATFORM. GOOGLE uses the data collected to analyze the PLATFORM's usage and to prepare reports which enable WIDETAIL to improve its services. Google Analytics integration is done in a way that keeps USERS' IP address anonymous by removing part of its information. You can find GOOGLE's privacy policy on [its website](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy);
  2. Mixpanel is a business analytics service provided by Mixpanel, Inc. ("MIXPANEL") used in the PLATFORM. It tracks user interactions with web and mobile applications and offers tools for targeted communication with them. Collected data is used to build custom reports and measure user engagement and retention. You can find MIXPANEL's privacy policy on [its website](https://mixpanel.com/privacy).

* * *

## Your Customers' Personal Data

Regarding your Customers's personal data, you accept that you are the controller of such personal data and you will comply with the applicable legislation.  
WIDETAIL will process such data on your behalf acting as your processor, accordingly with your instructions.  
If personal data sufficient to fulfill data requests cannot be exported from the PLATFORM, or requests for personal data erasure cannot be fulfilled, you can forward the request to WIDETAIL. If a Customer requests access to their personal data, you should first validate the identity of the requester.

* * *

## Disclosure to Third Parties

WIDETAIL does not sell or rent personal data to third parties, however, sharing of personal data may occur under the following conditions:

  1. WIDETAIL may rely on third parties for the provision of certain services on its behalf, and these third parties may have access to some personal data. WIDETAIL ensures that entities that have access to personal data are credible and offer high guarantees of protection, never transmitting more data than that which is necessary to provide the contracted service; and,  

  2. WIDETAIL may also transmit data to third parties regarding investigations, judicial enquiries and legal and/or administrative procedures, when ordered to do so by a court of law.

* * *

### Widetail's Subprocessors

WIDETAIL uses certain subprocessors to assist it in providing to its Merchants the Services as described in our Terms of Service. A subprocessor is a third party data processor engaged by WIDETAIL, who has or potentially will have access to or process USERS Content (which may contain Personal Data). WIDETAIL engages different types of subprocessors to perform various functions as explained in the below.

Subprocessor | Country | Purpose  
---|---|---  
Amazon Web Services, Inc. | EU | Cloud infrastructure & Storage  
Zendesk, Inc. | USA | Customer Support  
Mixpanel, Inc. | USA | Metrics  
Google, Inc. | USA | Email Service  
SendGrid | USA | Transactional & Email Marketing  
PipeDrive | USA | Sales Management  
InvoiceXpress | Portugal | Invoice Software.......  
Facto | Chile | Invoice Software.......  
  
## Third Parties Websites

The PLATFORM may contain links to other websites. These websites and the way they process collected information are the sole responsibility of their holders, and therefore, WIDETAIL is not responsible for their privacy policies and/or practices.

* * *

## Data Transfer

In the event of any personal data being transferred to third-parties in countries which are not Member states of the European Union, WIDETAIL will comply with the applicable legislation, in particular in regard to the adequate level of protection offered to personal data and the requirements for such transfers, not transferring personal data to jurisdictions that do not provide adequate safety and security guarantees.

* * *

## Residents of the European Union

If you are located in the European Union, you have certain rights under EU law with respect to your personal data, including the right to request access to, correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your personal data. If you are a Merchant, a Partner, a visitor of WIDETAIL's websites, or a user of the PLATFORM support services and wish to exercise these rights, please reach out using the contact form of this website. If you are a Customer and wish to exercise these rights, please contact the Merchants you interacted with directly -- WIDETAIL serve as a processor on their behalf, and can only forward your request to them, allowing the Merchant to respond.

Additionally, if you are located in the European Union, please note that WIDETAIL are generally processing your information in order to fulfill contracts WIDETAIL might have with you (for example if you if you are an USER of the PLATFORM), or otherwise to pursue WIDETAIL legitimate business interests listed above, unless WIDETAIL are required by law to obtain your consent for a particular processing operation.

* * *

## Changes to Privacy Policy

WIDETAIL reserves the right to adjust or amend this Privacy Policy at any time. WIDETAIL will give you notice of such changes by posting the revised policy on this Website, and where appropriate, by other means.

_Last Reviewed on 22nd May, 2018._
